<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sebastiaan Candel</title>
    <link>https://sebastiaancandel.nl/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sebastiaan Candel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 18:13:41 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sebastiaancandel.nl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>If data is the new oil, where is your industrial refinery?</title>
      <link>https://sebastiaancandel.nl/post/what_is_mlops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 18:13:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sebastiaancandel.nl/post/what_is_mlops/</guid>
      <description>This article was originally written for Deloitte by myself and my colleague Erik Bookholt, as posted in this article.
How DataOps and MLOps enable analytics at scale Back in 2006, Clive Humby coined the famous phrase “data is the new oil”, which was used to describe how data can be valuable. Fast forward to 2021 and many organizations have realized the role that (processed) data can play in gaining competitive advantage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://sebastiaancandel.nl/post/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 17:04:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sebastiaancandel.nl/post/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Hello, world! In an effort to improve my writing skills, a new blog is born!
For now, this post serves as an introduction of myself, and my blogging ambitions. I&amp;rsquo;m an ML engineer and Specialist Lead with Deloitte in The Netherlands, and this blog will cover any topic that I run into which might also be helpful, interesting or insightful to others.
What topics, you might ask? You could think about SQL tips &amp;amp; tricks, optimizations to Python code that are not obvious at first sight, or my foray into the world of MLOps; Bringing machine learning models to production environments in a sustainable, transparent, reproducible and automated manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Sebas</title>
      <link>https://sebastiaancandel.nl/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sebastiaancandel.nl/about/</guid>
      <description>Etiam porta sem malesuada magna mollis euismod. Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit. Donec id elit non mi porta gravida at eget metus. Donec sed odio dui.
Donec sed odio dui. Nulla vitae elit libero, a pharetra augue. Nulla vitae elit libero, a pharetra augue. Praesent commodo cursus magna, vel scelerisque nisl consectetur et.
Nulla vitae elit libero, a pharetra augue.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>